[
  {
    "questionNo": 1,
    "question": "They collected several colourful rocks but used some for decorating.<br>Fill in the empty box to find out how many rocks are left:",
    "options":["8","-","2","=",""],
    "answers": ["8","-","2","=","6"]

  },
  {
    "questionNo": 2,
    "question": "They found leaves and used some for their craft. Fill in the empty box to find out how many rocks are left:",
    "options":["10","-","6","=",""],
    "answers": ["10","-","6","=","4"]
    
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 3,
    "question": "They picked up a bunch of rocks to decorate their site and used some.Fill in the empty box to find the number of left rocks.",
    "options":["9","-","4","=",""],
    "answers": ["9","-","4","=","5"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 4,
    "question": "They found many shells for decorating the campsite and used a few. Fill in the answer in the empty box.",
    "options":["7","-","3","=",""],
    "answers": ["7","-","3","=","4"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 5,
    "question": "They brought lots of branches to decorate their tent and used some.Find the left branches.",
    "options":["11","-","6","=",""],
    "answers": ["11","-","6","=","5"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 6,
    "question": "They picked smooth stones for their campsite and used some.Fill in the answer in the empty box to find the left stones.",
    "options":["13","-","9","=",""],
    "answers": ["13","-","9","=","4"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 7,
    "question": "They gathered pine needles to decorate with and used some.Find the alpine needles that are left",
    "options":["14","-","9","=",""],
    "answers": ["14","-","9","=","5"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 8,
    "question": "They brought ribbons for decoration and used 12.Fill in the answer in the empty box to find the left ribbons.",
    "options":["17","-","12","=",""],
    "answers": ["17","-","12","=","5"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 9,
    "question": "They collected feathers to decorate the campsite and used a few. Fill in the answer in the empty box to find the left.",
    "options":["15","-","11","=",""],
    "answers": ["15","-","11","=","4"]
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 10,
    "question": "They picked up lanterns to brighten the campsite and hung a few.Fill in the box to find the left lanterns.",
    "options":["18","-","11","=",""],
    "answers": ["18","-","11","=","7"]
  }
]
